UTU New York State Legislative Director Files 5711
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Legislative Files. 1970-1973. (Box 4)
  - Senate 1335 (Hudson), Assembly 1481 (Kelleher): Switch Lights, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Senate 575 (Griffin), Assembly 2283 (Griffin): Train Length, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Assembly 227 (Tills): Weed and Vegetation, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Memorandum and letters etcetera regarding legislation, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Speed Indicator (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Requests for support of miscellaneous bills, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous Amendments, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Senate 2044 (Bernstein): Bus Recorder, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Senate 7556 (Bernstein) and Assembly 8679 (Lis): Bus Standee, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Assembly 171 (Cook) and Assembly 185 (Chananau): Code 42, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Re-introduction of Crew Consists, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Senate 484 (Gordon) and Assembly 9267 (Corbett): Flagging, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Senate 7586 (McGowan) and Assembly 8976 (Cook): Intercity Passenger Train Corporation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Senate 363 (Dunne) and 2103 (Galiber); Assembly 1699 (Mercorella): Jury Duty, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Assembly 810 (Carroll); Senate 206 (Warder) and 207 (Griffin): Meal Period, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Senate 1734 (Laverne) and Assembly 8885 (Carroll): Meal Period, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Legislative Files. 1973-1974. (Box 5)
  - Senate 1557 (Griffin) and Assembly 1811 (Lis): Railroad Safety, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Senate 537 (Giuffreda) and Assembly 403 (Ginsberg): Stone and Sand Cover, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Assembly 4270 (Drons) and Senate 2998 (Langley): Minimum Qualifications for Locomotive Engineers, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    March 2, 1971
  - Senate 709 (Hudson) and Assembly 691 (Kelleher): Switches, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Senate 8290 (Hudson) and Assembly 9277 (Sears): Speed Indicator, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Senate 7694 (McGowan) and Assembly 8793 (Tills): Vegetation and Debris, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Senate 7695 (McGowan) and Assembly 8777 (Lis and Cook): Obstruction of Crossings, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Senate 1557 (Griffin) and Assembly 1811 (Lis): To Amend Section 50 of the Public Service Law, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Senate 1589 (Griffin) and Assembly 1813 (Lis): Train Line Length, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University Budget Cuts, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Thruway Bill, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Speed Indicator Bill, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Legislative, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Memorandums, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Bills, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Legislation, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Assembly 1319 (Multi-Sponsored): Intercity Passenger Railroad Corporation, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Assembly 227 (Tills): Vegetation and Debris, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Senate 945 (Langley) and Assembly 1849 (Cook): Inspection of Locomotives, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Senate 3100 (Caliber) and Assembly 4924 (Stella): Jury Duty, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Senate 206 (Warder), Senate 207 (Griffin), and Assembly 810 (Carroll): Meal Period, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Senate 1670 (Langley et al) and Assembly 2332 (Sears et al): Speedometer, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Senate 1335 (Hudson) and Assembly 1481 (Kelleher): Switch Lights, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Package to G.W. Rogers, State Legislative Director from Sam J. Russo, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    January 23, 1973
  - Original Letters, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Senate 575 (Griffin): Train Line Length, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Senate 248 (Gordon) and Assembly 558 (Cook): Flagging, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Session of State Legislature, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Legislation, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Amend Transportation Law, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Senate-Assembly Transportation Bill, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    March 1974
  - Assembly 558 (Cook), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Senate 3100 (Galiber) and Assembly 4924 (Stella): Jury Duty, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Senate 1335-A (Hudson) and Assembly 1481-A (Kelleher): Lights on Switches, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Senate 206 (Warder) and Assembly 810 (Carroll); Senate 207 (Griffin) and Assembly 617 (Hausbeck): Meal Periods, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Senate 7020-7021 (Bloom) and Assembly 8215-8216 (Cincotta): School Bus Standees, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Senate 575 (Griffin) and Assembly 2283 (Griffin): Train Line Length, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Senate 5494 (Paterson) and Assembly 227 (Tills): Weed and Debris, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Assembly 12233 (Cook) and Senate 10597 (Griffin): Appropriation of Railway Education Council, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Senate 7829 and Assembly 9253: Regulation of lobbyist activities and repealing section 66, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    February 4, 1974
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Assembly 12233: Appropriation for the extension and subsidy of the Railway Education Council, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    REC established by the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University
- Legislative Files. 1975-1976. (Box 6)
  - Committee on Transportation, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Assembly 423 (Cook) and Senate 688 (Gordon): Flagging, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Investigation-Hearing Held in Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Package. February 28, 1975.
  - Assembly Task Force Subcommittee on Railroads, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Senate 334 (Griffin) and Assembly 1064 (Lill): Meal Period, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Assembly 3471-C (Graber) and Senate 2739-C (Mason): Missile Bill, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Session, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Session, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Senate 1620-A (Paterson) and Assembly 1883-A (Frey): Debris Bill, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Senate 629 (Hudson) and Assembly 421 (Kelleher): Lights on Switches, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Information Regarding Flagging Bill, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Flagging Bill Chapter 208, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Senate 7830 (Volker) and Assembly 9444 (Cook): Flagging, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Senate 62 (Bloom) and Assembly 48 (Cincotta): Safety Belts and Standees on School Buses, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Stoning of Trains, etcetera, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Senate 333 (Griffin) and Assembly 1776 (Griffin): Train Line Length, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Lobbying Registration Bill (Box 6, Folder 18)
    No date
  - Graber-Mason Vandalism Bill, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Assembly Sub-Committee Report on Railroads, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Legislative Files. 1972-1974. (Box 7)
  - Delinquent Assessment, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Closings of Locals (New York State), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Department of Transportation (Federal and State), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Department of Transportation Calendar of Hearings, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Endorsements, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Political Contribution Letters, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Kenneth R. Moore, Director, Bus Director: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Directory Changes, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - New York State Campaigns, Elections and Procedure Law, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Retroactive Pay, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship Fund - United Transportation Union, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Transportation Political Education League, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Catherine, Auxiliary President: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Department of State: J.F. Gezzi, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (New York State): Bulletins, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - New York State American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Convention, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    October 3, 4, 5, 1974
  - Newsletter: New York State Department of Labor, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Legislative Files. 1977. (Box 8)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Memorandums, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Session, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Senate and Assembly Public Hearings, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Alcoholism, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism in New York State: Programs, Problem, and Promise (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Bound. No date.
  - Alcoholism, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Package.
  - Health Insurance for Alcoholism, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Assembly 1541 (Nicolosi): Jury Duty, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Senate 3539 (Mason) and Assembly 4889 (Graber, Robach): Snowmobiles, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Senate 3539(Mason) and Assembly 4889 (Graber-Robach): Snowmobiles (continued), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Railway Studies Program, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Senate 3564 (Pisani-Volker) and Assembly 4887 (Graber-Robach): Pay Stubs, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Pay Stub Forms, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Senate 3564 (Pisani-Volker) and Assembly 4887 (Graber-Robach): Pay Check Stub Bill (Continued), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - School Bus Standees, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Senate 270 (Paterson) and Assembly 222 (Tills): Spark Arresters, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Senate 6227 (Present) and Assembly 7883 (Walsh): Tax Exemption Bill, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Senate 1923 (Paterson) and Assembly 2359 (Murphy): Gross Weight For Trucks, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Assembly 180: Regarding Insurance Agents, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Railroad Bills, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous United Transportation Union (UTU) Letters, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Vandalism, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Correspondence. 1963-1964. (Box 9)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) State Convention, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ladies Auxiliary, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Includes two bound volumes.
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Bulletins, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Includes bound constitution
  - New York State Association of Railroads, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Bus Department, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Legislative Board, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Special Circulars (C. Luna), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - National Legislation: Representative Al H. Chesser, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Circulars: Insurance Matters, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Circulars of Instruction, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Conferences: Representatives of other brotherhoods, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Subsidy: Niagara Frontier Port Authority, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Expenses, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - G.S. and T.W.E.B. Chase, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - President Charles Luna, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Political Information, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Presidential Railroad Commission, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Wage/Rules Negotiations, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Credentials: Reorganization Meeting, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Resolutions: Reorganization Meeting, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Increases in Per Diem, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Ladies' Auxiliary, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Bulletins, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - O'Connor-Samuels Campaign Material, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Includes newspaper clippings
  - Robert F. Kennedy, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Anthony J. Travia, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    April 1967
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Convention, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Bus Department, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Correspondence. 1964-1965. (Box 10)
  - Circular of Instructions, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Conferences: Legislative Representatives, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - National Convention, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Convention: Legislative Representatives, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    March 16-17, 1964
  - Correspondence: Legislative Board, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - W.E.B. Chase, General Secretary and Treasurer, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - A.H. Chesser, National Legislative Representative, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 8th Quadrennial Convention, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Reorganization Meeting: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Roll Call: 8th Quadrennial Session, New York State Legislative Board, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC): Orders and Miscellaneous Materials, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC): Accident Reports, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - C. Luna, President, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - E.A. Martin: Personal Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Testimonial Dinner: E.A. Martin, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    June 24, 1964
  - Newspaper Clippings of General Interest, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Political Information, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - State Endorsements, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Expenses, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Federal Endorsements, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Wage Rules, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Bulletins, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Legislative Board, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Bus Department, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Circulars of Instruction, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: Legislators, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Legislative Board, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Conference: Other Organizations, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Expenses, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Correspondence. 1965-1966. (Box 11)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer W.E.B. Chase, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Governor Rockefeller, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Orders - Miscellaneous Material, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Political Information, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - President C. Luna, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Accident Reports, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): State Convention, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - State Endorsements, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - National Legislative Representative A.H. Chesser, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): State Convention, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Legislative Board, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Board Assessment Files, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bus Department, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Legislators - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Legislative Bulletins, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Public Service Committee - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Board - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Bulletins, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Circulars of Instruction, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Election, Vacancy - Secretary of New York Legislative Board, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Expenses, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    Includes folders of time slips for the executive committee and board members.
  - State Endorsements, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Federal Legislation, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Federal Endorsements, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer W.E.B. Chase, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Governor Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Miscellaneous Material, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - President C. Luna, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - National Legislative Representative Chesser, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Political Information, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Accident Reports, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Correspondence. 1967-1968. (Box 12)
  - Health and Welfare Program, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Bulletins, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Legislative Bulletins, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Convention, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Circulars of Instruction, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Federal Legislation, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer W.E.B. Chase, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Governor Rockefeller, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission: Accident Reports, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - President C. Luna, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Department of Transportation, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Expense Statements, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League- Correspondence, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - National Legislative Representative A.H. Chesser, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Board - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee Meeting: Endorsements, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    August 15-17 1968
  - Original Membership Records of Legislative Representatives, Secretaries, Alternate Legislative Representatives, General Chairmen, etcetera, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Affiliation, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Bulletins, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Legislative Bulletins, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - New York State American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Per Capita Tax, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Committee: 33rd Convention, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Brotherhood Policy, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - National Legislative Representative A.H. Chesser, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Bus Department, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - By-Laws, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Circulars of Instruction, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Circulars: Individual Reserve, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence - Books of Law, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Public Service Committee - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Legislative Board - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Department of Transportation, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Executive Committee, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Federal Endorsements, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer W.E.B. Chase, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - New York State Senate and Assembly: Endorsements, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Correspondence. 1968-1969. (Box 13)
  - Congress and New York State Legislature, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Legislative Board, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Statements of Expense, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Representatives, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - John P. Lomenzo, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - President Charles Luna, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen: Newsletters, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Merger: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (BLF and E) - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen (ORC and B) - Switchmen's Union North America (SUNA), 1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions to the National Legislative Representative, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Niagara Frontier Local Chairmen Association, 1961-1968 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen: Membership Drive, 1962-1966 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Mary L. Roberts: Wage Claim, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Time Slips: Executive Committee, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Time Slips: Board Members, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Time Slips and Credentials: Reorganization Meeting, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League and Endorsement File, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO): Bulletins, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Business Department, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Chairman Election, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Bus Representative Election, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Competitive Transportation Paper, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    December 1969
  - National Legislative Representative A.H. Chesser, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Congressional Primaries, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Federal Department of Transportation, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - New York State Department of Transportation, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer: Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Frank Horton, Congressman, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Inspection Tour Notes, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Newsletters, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Charles Luna, President, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Howard J. Koch: General File, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - New York State Public Service Commission Calendar of Hearings, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Governor, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Scholarship Plans, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Special Expense Allotment, 1952-1968 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - General Secretary and Treasurer J.H. Shepherd, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Statements of Expense, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Correspondence. 1969-1971. (Box 14)
  - Time Slips: Board Members, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - United Transportation Union: News Articles, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - United Transportation Union: State Legislative Board, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - United Transportation Union: Newsletters, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Vice-Chairman Election, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Statement of Expense, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Trainmen's Political Education League: Recap by "T," "E," and "C" Locals, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 10)